Jhalar Hello friends I am Abhishek and
you are watching Sal problem friends and
everyone knows how big a problem a medical
policy or health insurance has in our life,
still friends a lot of
people are hesitant to invest in it, the
biggest reason for this is lack of knowledge
friends whenever any help viewers go to lunch
you have to go to some officer service road
but they have a lot of
time plans with a lot of options from a lot of packages
but you do not know the point on the
basis of which you have to choose a package
so friends in this video we will discuss
what is important a hello
viewers welcome in our life and will discuss
those points that you have to remember whenever
you go to buy a health insurance plan
then friends watch the video till the end
and if you have not subscribed to this channel yet then
please
subscribe and press the bell icon
because friends I will keep bringing
finance income tax GST video for you people the day after tomorrow
so
why is it important that Gurjar Samaj is in like
for this friends we will discuss on three points
The first point is stop
care, friends, health care facilities are getting
better and at the same time its cost
is increasing and if you have a good help
center package then you can fight this with the cost.
Number two is quality of
care, whenever it comes after help, first of all
we focus on quality and
you will get good quality light service at
a good place where you will
also have to pay the cost, so for this you
need a good health insurance
package. Number 3 President Income Situation
Friends, nowadays there is no statement of job, there is
no current, today is there, tomorrow is not there and
friends, look at today's situation, I
am in a long gown, business is closed, someone's job is gone
and what will happen if someone gets sick right now, so
here if you have a good
health insurance then you
can participate or there is a point which is
not done, that is 690 tax deduction on
friends, health is not just for this year, it is
such an investment that you will
not get your money back, but the benefit you will get is
much more than the money, so
friends, this was the importance of health
research now friends  We will discuss all those
points, you have to keep in mind whenever you go to
buy a health insurance plan, then first of all
you have to decide which plan you want,
Hindi Gurjar or just Total,
what is this, as the name suggests, this
plan is only for a single
individual,
not for the entire family and this is a little different, in
Total, in this, the entire family gets coverage in one moment,
whose name you will input, but remember one thing
friends, whatever is decided then
in Annual, it is decided on the basis of the
members whose age is the
highest, their premium will be decided on H only,
friends keep this in mind,
when choosing good hospitals for recruitment,
friends, here you have to do some homework
which is very essential, you need to know this,
if you or
any family member falls ill, then what will you do, you will
take them to the best hospital near you, you will go there and check, there is
no type of treatment with them, then your medical pass, then  You will have to
set aside money from your pocket
for two problems, so homework
is very important here, first of all you have to
make a list and in that list you have to
write the names of all those hospitals where
you will go whenever needed, whether it is
in your area, somewhere in Chat or
outside the stand, then friends you have to choose the
top five or six health
insurance explosive names with which those
hospitals are listed in the job,
then whatever I will tell you the checkers or
points, now you have to compare it with that, out of
those top five, which is the best for you,
friends, here you have to choose, I will
only tell you the points or
show you the status, friends, if you liked the video so far, then give
a like because
your one like will motivate me and I will be able to bring
even better videos for you, so
friends let's move ahead, friends, the
walking experiment, friends, what happens,
think today you bought a packet, but
friends, it is not like that you said that you got the money for the chemical app, you have to
wait for a time,
friends, this is called voting experiment, like
initial voting free mode, then play
that your first  It is 30 days, in that you
cannot do any film, you will
not get any money for the next Ambedkar, only if
you have an accident, then you
can bear the expenses of that kit, then
friends, the setting of pre-existing free
mode, then this club has to be submitted four times,
friends, then comes the meeting
free mode on Monday, for this you have to wait for three to four years,
after four years,
if there is any such policy, then you will
get the money for its plan, then friends, there is a
waiting period of 90 days for newborn baby,
friends, so you will have to go through all these things,
if you want to do this health inspector juice, then
friends, let's move ahead and the second
point is that they discuss what is a
pre-activated,
friends, this is a very important point and whenever
you get inspected, put your
pre-existing list of it in front of them,
friends, what is this, imagine that today
you went to the doctor, the doctor checked you
and the doctor said that you are a diabetic
patient, after 3 minutes you are doing a health
inspector juice, now you have diabetes,
your pre-existing disease health  Even
before doing the inspector juice, the
digit quality that you have is April as important as a system
disease, friends,
because its quantity, as I have already told you,
for someone it is 2 years in the last 4 years, maximum
four years from the system, so you have to
request chances and you will get its money only after four years, if you keep it, then
friends, do not hide it because if it is
found out later that you have hidden it and
you already had it, then friends,
you will not get a single penny of yours, keep this in mind,
Hello friends, whenever you go to plant any health issue, no matter which
company it is,
always keep one thing in mind, room
rent sub-limit, this is the room rent sub-limit that
you, every rescuer company
fixes a limit for room rent, now the limit,
whether it can be an amount or a
percentage, destroy all that, now
friends, why is room rent sub-limit so
important, why is a room rent
so important, why am I
emphasizing so much on this, think for yourself  The
bill of a hospital is more in camps,
when a doctor visits the Jain ward, he
charges more in camps or in
jail,
friends, the total cost of the hospital
depends on the total medical college,
you are definitely above that, but friends, the
inspector will love you as much as
your agreement and if you
choose a room whose rent is more than the agreement, then there was
a proportional amount of your love, they will
follow you, give an example, so
think, the Shubh limit is 2% and time is
injury and your Someshwar and left, then
how much has the birthday romance become, and you have chosen
a room whose rate is
less than this and your total
expenditure on oil, eyes, medical bills, hands and feet, then
friends, tell them the full amount that
you will get for the claim, but if you
choose a room which costs more than 350, that is, limit, then
you will not get the full claim,
friends, you will not get the full amount, you will get a post
amount, that ad like * forces means
120000 friends, you  You can see
how much loss you incurred by making 100 points and
how much claim amount you did not get. So
friends, therefore whenever you go to buy any package,
ask the broker what is the sub-limit of room rent.
If you find it suitable, then
buy it, otherwise do not buy it. The best thing is
that you buy a package in which there is
no sub-limit of Rs. 1000 per minute. Friends, the
premium will be higher. You will have to keep this in
mind. Friends, let me
discuss this important point here.
What
happens on deductible on insurance? In this, a 10% is fixed
which you will pay and the insurance company will pay on the balance amount.
For example, an agreement is made with you
that you will pay 10% on you
and the insurance company will pay on the remaining 90%.
Now, if the medical bill is 1 lakh, then you will
pay on 1000 and that company will pay on notification.
And if there is 1000 on medical, then
1000 will be charged on you and the insurance company will pay on 9000.
But the deductible here is a
little different here friends.  It is an
amount, not a percentage, that amount will be
agreed upon with you, it will be almost settled
and if you have to pay the amount first,
after that whatever balance is left will be paid by the
insurance company, it is different,
understand this friends, an
agreement has been made with you on the insurance company, there is a deductible of 30 thousand,
you will pay it first, now it is
5000, then 30, if you pay 20,000
on this company, if the bill is 2500, then
that company will not pay a single penny, you will have to
pay it from your pocket, so whenever you go to
buy a package, first of all
ask them what are their terms,
what are the terms of the deductible,
after that think about buying that package only after knowing,
friends, what is
Premchand Shiv, friends,
it indicates the performance of the company,
which company is providing the insurance service,
when you buy a package,
you will get a service bill
standing nearby, if the performance is not good then
what is the benefit of it from them, now
friends, its use is very important  Teacher is
number and limited divide on number fluid
pimple a service provider is
subscribing to it maya for stock now
it has settled dry ginger in it 15 or it
is lying in or you simply mean
now it means hatred towards it then cancel ok
so friends subscribe husband
stay away from him because
you will again have problem
in withdrawing money from them keep this in mind friends
height indicates that a company is
doing good work
and pink film Rishi Om friends this recipe
indicates the performance of the company and
how it is completed where obesity
divide by the amount of free membership
internet means how much amount of love the company is
packing and how many lovers it has to receive is its
review their glamorous
if the ICI of a company is more than hundred
means it is packing more cream products than the premium it is receiving
means the company is running the law in it if
someone's ICI is less than hundred means it means that he is only
thinking about his profit
friends he is only thinking about the amount of premium he receives  He is doing it
but when the time comes to do it on Prem mode,
he deletes it. If the
ICR of a company is 70%, it means that the person working in the company is
making profit and is
collecting Prem amount. So friends, whenever
you choose a company, take a good look at its main post. It
is Prince Post for Advance. What is this?
Friends, first of all, free medical checkup.
Whatever you have spent before the play store is
called previous
performance. But friends,
whenever you leave a particular date here, the last
three days of that will come on the date.
Whatever you have spent for 30 days after that will be
called free hospitalization
expenses. And here, and after that comes
friends, what is post post expenses? The
expenses incurred for seven days after medical checkup after discharge are
called post personal address
and there is a list of it, its details are there.
You should take complete information from them with your other agent
because whenever you
plan it, you will have to forget its proper information. You will have to go to
Arjun Bill, you will have to give the doctor's
certificate, after that you will have to pay this
amount.  You will get it friends, so the
whole trick about its happiness is from
here friends, that is cashless
reimbursement, which policy should you use now
friends, what happens in the year,
you fit in it, then you pay from your pocket,
then you pay the amount and then the
insurance company reimburses you,
but here it is mostly said
that whatever it is, 1 lakh, 2 lakh, 30
lakh, you have to pay from your pocket first,
but friends, cashless is not like that,
in cashless the insurance company directly transfers the
money to the hospital and this is
very helpful, but for this some paperwork has to be done,
some mistakes have to be followed,
friends, I will make a collector video of
my own person who will
send it after drinking it, so friends, always take a cashless
policy, take face pack juice and
ask these sports whether there is any facility in this package,
if yes then take it, otherwise do not take it,
friends, friends, this
premium friends, I have made one thing,
like a complaint, then there is your pocket for life time, there is
no fixed time for diet, it keeps on doing it according to your calculations,
hence you
Get a complete chart from your service provider about how much you will have to pay for
it, then it will be
easier for you to plan.
Friends, friends, what is power distribution? A
lot of the time, there are medical
expenses that you incur, but you
cannot do it for free. All those medical expenses
come under the permanent school center. Friends,
like if you had a cosmetic surgery, went to commit suicide, got injured,
spent money on it, you cannot do the problem,
chief dental treatment, sharing treatment, a
very big number list. So whenever you
want to choose one, first ask for a list
from your service center, according to that,
what are the
problems, which apps are there, which is
Paudwal Addison. Friends, now it comes,
so sisters, it is true that friends, you can bear the
entire cost of your medical bill.
If you do not subscribe like this, it
means you will not get it, you do not need
surgical equipment, then you have to subscribe button
there, do
not subscribe, find out all these scores, do
not subscribe ...  You
can do this, for this you will have to follow some important rules,
first of all,
when you apply a new product, the first thing for it is the
date of your internet service package, that means you have to remove the date, it is
happening on this, okay, from that fabric, first
you have to apply the network and you will feel like the new button,
inside it you will feel like whether
it is accepting or not,
if it is accepting then it is fine, if it is
not accepting then you will have to
work with the old one,
now friends, whatever you apply, the
name of the thing service voter, your work is going on right now, you will have to give its total to everyone,
now friends, I am coming to the western free
mode, I have already told you that this is the
initial voting, Priya and then
Pimpri and already aware of the old, with the
old versions, they have crossed all the Harding
Road,
with their new product, no such
voting free mode will be applicable to you,
this is a good point, and
look at it carefully and follow Jaipur city,
friends
Hello friends, how did you like today's video?
If you liked it, then please do not
forget to like it and whatever points I have mentioned,
watch it once again and note it down and
if you feel that this will be useful to you or any of your friends, then do
share it and do not
forget to subscribe. Friends,
that's all for today. Thank you friends, thank you very much.